Trip to Switzerland!
On the way to the main train station
Sandwich for breakfast
Now off to Switzerland!
I’m going on this trip with a friend who is also graduating this semester
It’s been 7 years since I first came to Germany
And I didn’t get to travel a lot
Since this is my last year in Freiburg and Switzerland is super close by
I spontaneously decided to go to Switzerland as a graduation trip
Scenery outside makes me super excited
About 3 hours later, we’re in Interlaken
We have some time left till the check in
So we decided to put our bags in the locker and went to have lunch
It’s just like a painting
It really feels like we’re in Switzerland 🇨🇭
We didn’t plan anything too specific so we’re walking towards the city center
Perfect weather✨
Even the color of the lake is pretty
We’re getting close to the center
You can even see people paragliding🪂
Wow,,
Me as a tourist couldn’t just pass by the gift shop
They have cute little fondue pots too
Cute plates
Now we’re trying to decide what to eat
It’s so peaceful💫
We decided to go for a steak
But the beef ragout looks so good too so we got one of those
Everywhere we go, you can see these crazy mountains
But it was getting hot,, so we’re on a hunt for Ice Americano 🥵
We just went into the cafe and asked if she could make us an ice coffee and she said yes
Swiss people are so sweet🥺
Back to the train station
The view to our Airbnb
And now we’re getting on a bus
The bus seems pretty similar to the German buses
And we’re here!!! The place seems straight out of a story book
The top floor is our place
Up the stairs
Tada
We booked a relatively cheap place so we didn’t expect too much out of it
But the view here is amazing✨
And from this room
You can see a little hill
Cute little bathroom
After getting unpacked, we’re on the way to grocery shopping
Struggling to open this little gate
View from the bus stop (Swiss ver.)
We chose the scenery over convenient location
So we have to take the bus and the train to go the supermarket
We’re here!
Some flat peaches
Eggs
most importantly,, pork belly!
The train back to Airbnb comes every hour,, we just missed one
So we googled and it says that there’s a gondola takes us to the bus stop instead of train
On the way to catch the gondola 🚡
It was so hot and the stuff was heavy going up the hill
All the way up here!!
And,, gondola was closed,,
We hiked the hill for nothing
But we found a statue of Sherlock Holmes on the way back
Apparently the waterfall where Sherlock Holmes died is in this town
And there was a Sherlock Holmes museum but it was already closed
At least we get to see this scenery
It’s okay cuz we’re on a vacation
So we have enough time to spare
We just got on the next train back to our Airbnb
First dinner in Swiss
Noodle + pork belly
We brought some food with us since everything is so expensive here
We came prepared with toast bread and jam
The menu isn’t too Swiss but
With some pork belly
Cheers to our grad trip 🥂
Second day in Switzerland
First thing in the morning to check scenery outside
Some fresh air
It rained a little so we decided to take our time till we head out
For brunch,, ramen noodles
It cleared up again 🌞
Back to our bus stop
Today we’re going to Iseltwald where Crash landing on you was filmed
It was soooooo hot
Waiting in the shades
Picture time
On the bus
And on the train
And there’s two way to get there : train and ferry
So we decided to take the ferry
The train is shaking like crazy
We’re getting close
Here at the ferry dock
I think this is the ship that’s going to take us there
And this scenery is so unforgettable
We didn’t really plan this trip thoroughly
We just thought it to be pretty but the scenery is crazy
Even this ferry.. we just took it cuz it was the fastest way to get there
And now we get to see this unforgettable view
There was no place to sit
So we walked around
I wanted to come back here with my family
Iseltwald!
This is where he played the piano in Crash landing on you 🎹
I actually haven’t seen the show
Iseltwald was quite small and that was all they have
But still the scenery was so beautiful
Since the people are lining up to take pictures we decided to get coffee first
People on the ferry are waving so I waved them back
One of the ignorant kids did the chinky eye with his fingers
I still regret not flipping him off
Let’s try not to ruin my mood cuz of one ignorant person’s disrespectful behavior
Back to the photo zone 📸
It was our turn to take a picture
But one lady started to getting tanned after laying down her towel in the middle of the deck
So we waited for nothing and took our picture in the corner of the deck
It’s time to go home
Back on the ferry
And to the train
And we’re in Interlaken for dinner
It seems familiar now
But still had to stop by the gift shop
So I got a new postcard
We came here for Haxen but it’s only available in the weekend
Barbecue rib!
The beer was good and the rib was also really good
Second round is Guinness
Now back to our Airbnb
This spot is where all the paragliders land
We were exhausted on the way back
Another train ride
Bus ride
Went to bed right off
Last day
So peaceful
Getting ready for breakfast
Ice tea from Germany
And we’re almost emptying our fridge
I got this now
And the view is breathtaking
We’re going to Luzern today
Train ride is always fun and beautiful
It really seems like a city
We’re here in Luzern!
It’s such a city compared to last to yesterday
Carpel bridge and a herd of maggots
There were so many
But the bridge was still pretty
Once crossed the bridge
We’re going to Starbucks
Why is Starbucks even so pretty here in Switzerland
should I get one...
Terrace outside isn’t that romantic nor great
Cuz of all the pigeons
I loved coffee time here
More scenery
It was so pretty everywhere we go
How is this possible
On our way to see the Lion sculpture
This was made to commemorate Swiss soldiers who died during the French Revolution
I thought it’d be one of those disappointing/ overrated statues in Europe
But is was so much bigger than what I expected and the face of the lion was impressive
To the food court for lunch
We’re not too desperate for Swiss food so we’re just going to get something from here
It was better than what I expected 👀
It was pretty good actually!
It was getting really hot so we decided to go back
On the way to the main train station
It was for a brief visit but I think Luzern is a beautiful city where I can see myself living here
I even googled whether they have master program for psychology
We had some time left till our train
So we went shopping to the gift store
Another postcard
Since it’s too hot out
We’re back in another Starbucks
And I got the Luzern cup from here!
Now on the way to the train
Views from the train >>>>>>>
This is also a place where they filmed crash landing on you
But it was too hot so we’re just going to pass by
Bus ride back to our Airbnb
And the way back
We almost melted cuz of the heat 🥵
Chilling a little till the sun goes down
Last walk around
And now to packing
Last dinner was leftover pork belly
With cup noodles
Chatting with my friend
And calling it a day watching our favorite show 💫
Last breakfast in Switzerland
We finished all the food we brought
Now it’s time to go back home
View out of the window for the last time
It’s been real
Leaving notes
Returning the keys
Hard goodbye to this beautiful place
I liked everything about this trip
I always felt a little unease after traveling
But maybe because of the person I was with
Or because of the location I chose
Or maybe because it was a trip after graduating
I was able to truly enjoy the trip from the beginning
Even though I thought of my family back home throughout the trip
I’m going to take them here for sure someday
On the train back to Freiburg
It’s really time to say goodbye to Switzerland
And we’re here in Freiburg again!
Back to my daily life
And back to home